(Sheldon:)I'll play along. Ow.
(Sheldon:)I had an unusual experience
with Amy last night.
(Leonard:)Really? How could you tell?
(Sheldon:)She was attempting
to engage me in gossip.
Mm. You don't say.
Yes.
(Sheldon:)I think prolonged exposure
to Penny
(Sheldon:)has turned her into a bit
of a Gabby Gertie.
(Leonard:)So, what's the gossip?
(Sheldon:)Oh, please, I was just
pointing it out.
(Sheldon:)I have no desire to engage
in the activity.
(Leonard:)Fine, don't tell me.
(Sheldon:)All right, get this.
(Amy:)Bernadette is thinking
about breaking up with Howard.
(Sheldon:)Oh...
(Leonard:)That's too bad.
I wonder what happened.
(Sheldon:)Mm, it's hard to say.
I can only speculate
(Sheldon:)based on the data I collected
(Sheldon:)watching my parents' marriage
implode.
(Sheldon:)In that case,
the woman dives into religion,
(Sheldon:)while the man dives
into a bottle-blonde bartender
(Sheldon:)who tries to buy my love
with action figures.
(Sheldon:)Oop! Out of arrows.